<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Appraisers>
  <Appraiser id="Rick_Lifferth">
    <Name>Rick R Lifferth</Name>
    <Certifications>MAI, SRA</Certifications>
    <ImgId>RickLifferth</ImgId>
    <Description><![CDATA[Rick graduated from Brigham Young University in 1973 with a Bachelor's of Arts.  In 1975, he received an MBA from Indiana University.  He started appraising (part time) while attending graduate school in 1973.  He quickly recognized the need for organized, accurate data sources that are efficient and easy for appraisers to use.  In 1980 he founded <strong>Market Data Service, LLC</strong> (MDS) to fill this need.  During his 39 year career, he has achieved the MAI and SRA designations and specializes in residential related property appraisals.  He has also held a real estate salesman's license for 36 years.  He has served on the local MLS committee.  He has been active in government relations issues.  He served for 6 years on the Government Relations committee of the Appraisal Institute.  He served on the Utah Appraiser Certification Board for 6 years and has also served as President of Utah Association of Appraisers. Rick and Kathy are the parents of 6 children and they have 18 grandchildren.  In his spare time, he enjoys bike riding and spending time with his family. ]]></Description>
  </Appraiser>
  <Appraiser id="Gentry_Lawson">
    <Name>Gentry Lawson</Name>
    <Certifications>Certified Appraiser</Certifications>
    <ImgId>GentryLawson</ImgId>
    <Description><![CDATA[Gentry began his appraising career in 2006, just shortly after completing a bachelors degree in Business Finance from Weber State University.  He started as an entry level worker and learned the industry from the bottom up.  While apprenticing, Gentry completed his Master's of Business Administration from Weber State University.  Gentry is a certified appraiser with the state of Utah, is an associate member of the Appraisal Institute and is a licensed title searcher.  He understands the importance of business relationships and is dedicated to providing customers with a timely and accurate appraisal.  In his spare time Gentry enjoys being active in the outdoors.]]></Description>
  </Appraiser>
  <Appraiser id="Eric_Larson">
    <Name>Eric Larson</Name>
    <Certifications>Trainee</Certifications>
    <ImgId>EricLarson</ImgId>
    <Description><![CDATA[Eric began working in the appraisal industry in September of 2013.  He is currently working on his experience hours to become Lifferth Appraisal’s next certified residential appraiser.  He is recognized as an Appraiser Trainee with the state of Utah and is working hard to earn his first designation.  He is also a full-time student at the University of Utah studying Hospitality Management.  Eric intends to further his education through a Master’s program once his Bachelor’s degree is complete.  When Eric is not busy with school and work he can be found doing photography with his wife, playing football, working on cars or experiencing the great outdoors.]]></Description>
  </Appraiser>
</Appraisers>
